# JENNA HALLAM

12772 Wembly Rd, Carmel, IN 46033 | (317) 681-9164 | Hallam8492@gmail.com | LinkedIn

#### **Summary**

Professional with 10 years of combined IT and customer service experience looking to translate coding and people skills into a career as a developer. As an instructor for Eleven Fifty Academy's software development program, I am poised and ready to put hard-earned skills into practice.

## **Skills & Highlights**

- Languages: C#, HTML5, CSS, APEX, SOQL
- Frameworks: Entity Framework, .NET , Lightning Component Framework
- **Methodologies:** Agile (Scrum, Kanban)
- Environments: Visual Studio Community 2019, Visual Studio Code, Salesforce Lightning
- API Testing: Postman API, Swagger
- **ORMs:** Entity Framework, LINQ
- **Design Patterns:** MVC, N-tier Architecture, Repository Pattern
- **Services:** GitHub, Azure (deployment)

## **Professional Experience**

## Eleven Fifty Academy (Indianapolis, IN)

Aug 2020 - Present

*Instructor (Software Development)* 

- Support up to 60 students through their enrollment in the Software Development program. Coach through debugging, C# syntax, and fundamentals.
- Provide support to students by checking in to gauge progress and improvement throughout the program.

## Dia&Co (Remote)

Jan 2018 - Apr 2019

Stylist

- Selected clothing items tailored to each customer's preferences and performed at or above sales performance standards every month.
- Reported bugs to the development team on a daily basis when interacting with the agent dashboard.

#### **GEICO** (Carmel, IN)

Feb 2014 - Feb 2016

Licensed Insurance Representative

- Obtained Insurance Producer's License in over 10 states and maintained continuing education requirements.
- Received "Cream of the Crop" award (twice) for achieving a place in the top three agents based on metrics.
- Handled 50+ calls per day while maintaining state-specific guidelines and procedures.

#### **Education**

# **Salesforce and Deloitte Pathfinder Program**

Oct 2020 - Feb 2021

Graduate

- Relevant coursework: Apex programming, Salesforce Lightning
- **Certifications:** Platform Developer 1 (in progress)

#### Eleven Fifty Academy (Indianapolis, IN)

Apr 2020 - Jul 2020

Software Development Program

Awards: Core Value Award for Leadership

- **Relevant coursework:** Database Design and Development, Data Management, Object-oriented programming logic
- Related Projects: Developed vocabulary flash card website using asp.net